Guide to the Shael Shapiro Papers MSS.200
Fales Library and Special Collections
Shael Shapiro Papers
1965-2006
Fales Library and Special Collections
Shapiro, Shael
MSS.200
54 Linear Feet in 23 records cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 83 rolled storage boxes.
7.16 Megabytes in 5 floppy disks.
Shael Shapiro is an architect who was instrumental in the writing and passage of the so-called "Loft Law" that in 1971 allowed artists to legally live in downtown Manhattan lofts. The collection contains architectural drawings and reproductions of numerous buildings throughout New York City and records documenting Shapiro's SoHo based architectural practice from the 1970s to the early 2000s. The bulk of the records are paper with some born-digital materials.
Scope and Content Note
The Shael Shapiro Papers consists of architectural drawings and reproductions, correspondence, building specifications, photographs (primarily building exteriors and interior details), inspection reports, architect's and engineer's reports, floppy disks, financial and legal documents related to his architectural practice on Wooster Street in the SoHo neighborhood of Manhattan, N.Y. from the 1970s to the early 2000s. The architectural drawings and reproductions found in the collection include floor plans, elevations, details, structural, plumbing and mechanical drawings, and some sketches. Most reproductions are diazotypes or ink on plastic, and most original drawings are graphite and/or ink on paper or on plastic. Some architectural drawings and reproductions were produced by consulting engineering firms, most often by WYS Design Partnership, Consulting Engineers. The collection also contains New York City Department of Building applications, permits and certificates, documents and correspondence with the City of New York Landmarks Preservation Commission, as well as correspondence and registrations with the New York City Loft Board. Although Shapiro's most notable work is the conversion of lofts in downtown Manhattan, the collection contains material related to projects (identified by job number and address) throughout New York City.
Biographical Note
Shael Shapiro is an architect whose practice was largely based in the SoHo neighborhood of Manhattan, N.Y. He studied architecture at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, in Troy, N.Y., and moved to SoHo in 1967, living in one of the artist George Macuinas's Flux Houses on Wooster Street. Shapiro worked on architectural projects throughout New York City, but his most significant work was focused on artists' lofts in downtown Manhattan. Shapiro was instrumental in the writing and passage of the so-called "Loft Law," enacted in 1971, which allowed artists to legally live in lofts downtown, and helped shape the growing community of artists in 1970s SoHo.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open without restrictions. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Shael Shapiro in 2007. The accession number associated with this gift is 2007.200.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted.
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Architecture -- New York (State) -- New York.; Architectural drawings (visual works); Architectural records.; Artists and community -- New York (State) -- New York; SoHo (New York, N.Y.); Artists -- Dwellings -- New York (State) -- New York.; Architecture, Modern -- 20th century.; Lofts -- Law and legislation -- New York (State) -- New York.; New York (N.Y.). Landmarks Preservation Commission; New York (N.Y.). Department of Buildings
- Architectural Records
  - Job: 0211, 116 Tenth Avenue, Susan's Gallery, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Job: 8228, 93-99 Greene Street, 1983-1986 (Box 1)
  - Job: 8229, 515 Broadway, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Job: 8311, 53 Mercer Street, 1983-1987 (Box 1)
  - Job: 8302, 480-482 Broadway, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Job: 9508, 114 East 32nd Street, 1995-1997 (Box 1)
  - Job: 9606, 17 Thompson Street, 1996-1998 (Box 1)
  - Job: 9629, 39-45 Vestry Street, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Job: 8804, 164-165 Perry Street, 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - Job: 9908, 139-141 Franklin Street, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Job: 8943, 475 West Broadway, 1984-1990 (Box 1)
  - Job: 8923, 543 Broadway, Rockwell Loft, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Job: 8933, 105-111 Wooster Street, 1989-1991 (Box 1)
  - Job: 0020, 50 Bond Street, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Job: 9124, 20 East 20th Street, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Job: 9119, 167 Perry Street, 1991-1993 (Box 2)
  - Job: 8542, 285 West Broadway, 1985-1989 (Box 2)
  - Job: 8523 A 398 West Broadway / 8523 B, 76 Thompson, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Job: 9118, 480 West Broadway, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Job 9133, 398 Broadway, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Job: 8930, Olcott Hotel, 1995-1997 (Box 2)
  - Job: 9609, 333 Hudson Street, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Box 24)
  - Job: 9531, 630 West 52nd Street, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Job: 9806, 247 Mullberry Street, 1998-2001 (Box 2)
  - Job: 9809, 321A Greenwich Street, 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Job: 9808, 433 Broadway, 1996-1998 (Box 2)
  - Job: 0220, 510 Broadway, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Job: 0007, 21 Astor Place, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Job: 9003, 239 & 247-253 West 116th Street, 1990-1993 (Box 2)
  - Job: 9626, 39-45 Vestry Street, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Job: 8649, 518-556 West 57th Street aka 503-561 West 56th Street, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Job: 7862, 383 West Broadway, 1979-1990 (Box 3)
  - Job: 8425, 627 Greenwich Street, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Job: 8227, 537 Broadway, 1983-1995 (Box 3)
  - Job: 9217, 40 Renwick Street, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
  - Job: 9205, 719 Greenwich Street, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
  - Job: 9027, 351 West Broadway, 1985-1993 (Box 3)
  - Job: 9028, 421 West Broadway, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Job: 8731, 480 West Broadway, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Job: 9227, 22 North Moore Street, 1997-1999 (Box 4)
  - Job: 9234, Schur Loft, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Job: 7436, Long Island City Medical, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Job: 7437, 440 Lafayette Street, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Job: 7438, 97 Wooster Street, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
  - Job: 7440, 122 Spring Street, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Job: 7444, 70 Grand Street, 1975-1980 (Box 4)
  - Job: 9234, 115 Wooster Street, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Job: 9244, 49 East 67th Street, undated (Box 4)
  - Job: 9250, 552 West 43rd Street, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
  - Job: 9235, 153 Hudson Street, 1992-1997 (Box 4)
  - Job: 8614, 383 Lafayette Street, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Job: 8618, 211 West Broadway, 1980-1992 (Box 4)
  - Job: 8620, 83 Murray Street, 1986-1993 (Box 4)
  - Job: 8925, 482 Broadway, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Job: 8625, 165 Perry Street, 1986-1989 (Box 4)
  - Job: 8930 A, Olcott Hotel, 1985-1995 (Box 4)
  - Job: 7410, 54 East 11th Street, Gene Eagles Loft, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7421, 42 West 15th Street, 1974-1978 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7419, 155 Wooster Street, 1977-1979 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7418, 141 Prince Street, 1974-1978 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7426, 52 White Street, 1974-1978 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7425, 451 West Broadway, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7424, 53 Greene Street, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7423, 719 Greenwich Street, 1974-1983 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7433, 89 West 3rd Street, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7432, 123 Prince Street, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7430, Fieldcrest Shop, Copenhagen, undated (Box 5)
  - Job: 7428 / 7429 / 7738, 424 Greenwich Street, 1980-1983 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7429, 424 Greenwich Street, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7427, 431 West Broadway, 1972-1975 (Box 5)
  - Job: 9020, 383 West 12th Street, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Job: 9016, 140 Grand Street, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Job: 9017, Eagle Tenants Corp., 1979-1990 (Box 5)
  - Job: 7936 / 9610, 351 West Broadway, 1980-1996 (Box 5)
  - Job: 9626, 39-46 Vestry Street, 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - Job: 8929, 111 Fifth Avenue, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Job: 9626, 39 Vestry Street, 1997-1999 (Box 6)
  - Job: 9411, 66 Grand Street, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Job: 9414, Schur Warehouse, undated (Box 6)
  - Job: 9034, 482 Broome Street, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Job: 9711, 359 West 11th Street, 1987-1997 (Box 6)
  - Job: 8643, 36 Lispenard Street, 1979-1988 (Box 6)
  - Job: 8640, 90 Thompson Street, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Job: 8634, 54 Bleecker Street, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Job: 9426, 116 Hudson Street, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Job: 9428, 14 East 33rd Street, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Job: 8639, 983 Third Avenue, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Job: 8113, 28 East 4th Street, 1982-1987 (Box 6)
  - Job: 7402, 114 Spring Street, 1974-1978 (Box 6)
  - Job: 7413, 4 East 77th Street, 1965-1974 (Box 6)
  - Job: 7412, 510 Broadway, 1969-1974 (Box 6)
  - Job: 7411, 115 Spring Street, 1974-1980 (Box 6)
  - Job: 9425, 285 Lafayette Street, old alterations, 1980, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Job: 8019, 704 Broadway, 1980-1982 (Box 7)
  - Job: 9812, 14-22 Leonard Street, undated (Box 7)
  - Job: 8816, 704 Broadway, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Job: 8832, Kenin Loft, 1978-1989 (Box 7)
  - Job: 9307, 118 Spring Street, 1993-1995 (Box 7)
  - Job: 9400, 426-428 Broome Street / 38 North Moore Street, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Job: 9309, 150 East 61st Street, 1978-1994 (Box 7)
  - Job: 8015, 205 East 22nd Street, 1980-1983 (Box 7)
  - Job: 7444, 64-70 Grand Street, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Job: 7435, 43 West 13th Street, 1975-1984 (Box 8)
  - Job: 9229, 524 Broadway, 1994-1997 (Box 8)
  - Job: 9227, 38 North Moore Street, 1992-1995 (Box 8)
  - Job: 8537, 400 West Broadway, 1986-1991 (Box 8)
  - Job: 8511, 167 Perry Street, 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Job: 7626, 75-81 Grand Street, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7312, 485 Broome Street, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7307, 16-18 Greene Street, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7306, 345 West Broadway, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7309, 451 West Broadway, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7525, 457-461 West Broadway, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7529, 125 Prince Street, 1975-1985 (Box 9, Box 24)
  - Job: 7303, 138 Sullivan Street, 1974-1977 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7510, 476 Broome Street, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7446, 431 Broadway, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7505, 129 East 15th Street, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7532, 68 Jane Street, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7601, PS1 Institute for Art & Urban Resources, 1975-1982 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7613, 30-34 West 13th Street, 1972-1978 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7840, 134-140 Grand Street, 1980-1982 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7845, 142 Fifth Avenue, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7841, 451 Washington Street, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7842, 91 Hudson Street, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7843, 55 North Moore Street, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7846, 716 Broadway, 1978-1981 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7836, 165 Spring Street, 1978-1986 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7835, Keene Chop House, undated (Box 9)
  - Job: 7833, 366 Broadway, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7836, 165-169 Spring Street, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Job: 8706, 99 Wooster Street, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Job: 7626, 75-87 Grand Street, 1977-1980 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7628, 530 LaGuardia Place, 1977-1979 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7629, 460 Broome Street, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7630, 7-13 Worth Street, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7632, 423 Broome Street, 1977-1984 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7635, 482 Broadway, 1977-1981 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7618, 54 Franklin Street, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7621, 226 Lafayette Street, 1973-1976 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7625, 158 Franklin Street, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Job: 7603, 465 West Broadway, 1977-1979 (Box 10)
  - Job: 8205, 84 Wooster Street, 1988-2000 (Box 10)
  - Job: 8203, 15 West 18th Street, 1982-1993 (Box 10)
  - Job: 8202, 95 Fifth Avenue, 1982-1990 (Box 10)
  - Job: 9026, 561 Broadway, The Singer Building, 1993-1996 (Box 10)
  - Job: 9820, 90 John Street, 1999 (Box 10)
  - Job: 8723, 42 West 48th Street, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Job: 9006, 135 West 22nd Street, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Job: 9013, Downtown Realty, 1986-1990 (Box 10)
  - Job: 9005, 519 East 82nd Street, 1984-1990 (Box 10)
  - Job: 8920, Puck Building, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Job: 8919, 501-507 Eighth Avenue, 1984-1990 (Box 10)
  - Job: 9629, 351 West Broadway, 1998 (Box 11, Box 24)
  - Job: 8654, 361 Broadway, 1984-1991 (Box 11)
  - Job: 8807, 465 West Broadway, 1987-1994 (Box 11)
  - Job: 8813, 140 West 58th Street, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Job: 0205, 17 Vestry Street, 1985-2001 (Box 11)
  - Soho Infill Zoning, undated (Box 11)
  - Job: 8714, 316-320 East 86th Street, 1987-1989 (Box 11)
  - Job: 8904 / 7912, 24 West 12th Street, 1977-1989 (Box 11)
  - Job: 8707, 860 Broadway, 1987 (Box 11)
  - Job: 8841, 670 Broadway, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8844, 1221 Sixth Avenue, Kellwood Co., 1988 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8404 / 8903 475 West Broadway, 1984-1990 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8928, 172 Norfolk Street, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8918, 400 West Broadway, 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8926, 107 Grand Street, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Job: 9026, 561 Broadway, The Singer Building, 1979-1996 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8401, 34 Hubert Street, 250 West Street, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8406, 60 Thompson Street, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8409, 161 Perry Street, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8708, 102-106 Wooster Street, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8841, 670 Broadway, 1986-1989 (Box 12)
  - Job: 8316, 382 West Broadway, 1983-1985 (Box 12)
  - Job: 7838, 114 East 36th Street, 1977-1981 (Box 13)
  - Job: 9816, 220 West 19th Street, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Job: 9819, 99 Park Avenue South, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Job: 9918, 254 West 54th Street, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - Job: 9227, 38-40 North Moore Street, 1989-1991 (Box 13)
  - Job: 9223, 317-319 Greenwich Street, 1990-1993 (Box 13)
  - Job: 7836, 165-169 Spring Street, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Job: 7840, 134-140 Grand Street, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Job: 7839, Dignan's Loft, 1978-1979 (Box 13)
  - Job: 7864, 105 Mercer Street, 1971-1981 (Box 13)
  - Job: 7867, 33 Bleecker Street, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Job: 7771, 10 East 44th Street, 1954, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7722, 78 Grand Street, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7774, 31 West 31st Street, 1977-1979 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7770, 465 Washington Street, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7769, 143 Prince Street, 1977-1980 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7762, 2061 Broadway, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7759, Sheer House, undated (Box 14)
  - Job: 7766, 71 Hudson Street, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7767, 447 Broome, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7768, 540 LaGuardia, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7763, 542 Broadway, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7762, 2061-2065 Broadway, 1976-1979 (Box 14)
  - Job 7758, 90 West Broadway, 1979-1987 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7753, 429 West Broadway, 1975-1979 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7756, 413 Greenwich Street, 1977-1981 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7756, 413 Greenwich Street, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7746, 417 West Broadway, 1977-1980 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7747, 527 West 34th Street, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7750, 109 West 26th Street, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7751, 48 Beach Street, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7745, 1 Gramercy Place, 1974-1978 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7744, 812 Greenwich Street, Cameron Loft, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7743, Tribeca Brochure, undated (Box 14)
  - Job: 7919, 20-24 North Moore Street, 1979-1981 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7918, Teitelbaum Weiss Loft, 1978-1979 (Box 14)
  - Job: 7910, 462-464 Broome Street, undated (Box 15)
  - Job: 7911, 118-120 Fifth Avenue, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7913, 105 Fifth Avenue, 1979-1981 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7915, 412 East 73rd Street, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7916, 1200 Broadway, Stern Loft, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7917, 20 East 20th Street, 1979-1990 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7805, 9-13 Maiden Lane / Job: 7937, 143-149 West 29th Street, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7715, 120 Liberty Street, 1977-1980 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7714, 101 Prince Street, 1977-1985 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7713, 308 East 49th Street, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7712, 149 West 24th Street, 1977-1985 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7700, Miscellaneous Jobs 1977 (Box 15)
  - Job: 7711, 154-156 West 27th Street, 1970-1978 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7710, 105 Hudson Street, 1977-1979 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7709, 142 Greene Street, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7708, 28 East 4th Street, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7707, 812 Greenwich Street, Judith Brown Loft, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7704, Koffsky, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7702, 110 Hudson Street, 1977-1979 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7642, 62 East 1st Street, 1975-1977 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7636, 407-411 Greenwich Street, 1980, 2002 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7715, 120 Liberty Street, 1977-1980 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7718, 163 Grand Street, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7717, 474-478 West Broadway, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7721, 34 East 30th Street, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7722, 78 Grand Street, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7723, 477 Broome Street, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7724, Blumberg Bedroom, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7725, 143 West 20th Street, 1977-1980 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7726, 141-145 West 17th Street, 1977-1979 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7727, 14 West 17th Street, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7728, 441 Lafayette Street, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7729, 139 Spring Street, 1978-1988 (Box 16)
  - Job: 7742, 6-8 West 20th Street, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7740, 143 Prince Street, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7738, 424 Greenwich Street, 1978-1984 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7737, 457 Broome Street, 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7736, 34 West 31st Street, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7734, 139-149 West 19th Street, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7735, 147 West 22nd Street, 1978-1992 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7733, 22 West 30th Street, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7731, 1225 Broadway, 1976-1979 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7730, 62 Greene Street, 1979-1981 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7120, 451 West Broadway, Showroom for Adel Rootstein, 1976 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7119, 30-34 West 13th Street, 1972-1978 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7118, 919 Third Avenue, 1971 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7217, 8 West 13th Street, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7113, 330 Broome Street, 1973 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7221, 637-649 West 125th Street, Reality House Inc., 1972 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7208, 53 Mercer Street, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7908, 54 Fifth Avenue, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7215, 325 West End Avenue, Hecht Apartment, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7213, City Walls, Frosty Meyers Wall, 1972-1975 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7205, 539 West 45th Street, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7204, 118 Forsyth Street, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7401, 451 West Broadway, John Stern's Loft, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7363, 407-411 Greenwich Street, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7320, Plaza Theater, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Job: 7319, 1 Gramercy Park, undated (Box 17)
  - Job: 7318, 28 Howard Street, 1970-1974 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7317, 83 Wooster Street, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7405, 10 Bleecker Street, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7403, 70 Greene Street, 1969-1974 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7402, 114 Spring Street, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Professional Liability Insurance Coverage, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Department of Buildings documents, various projects, 1972-1977 (Box 18)
  - Design Data, undated (Box 18)
  - 542 Broadway, Caryatids of Broadway, 1974-1977 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7004, 47 Saint Marks Place, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7003, Ordover House, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7001, 21 Bond Street, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - 267 West 43rd Street, Dr. Schreiber's Office, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7105, 113-121 Prince Street, Tri-Prince Coop, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7009, 485 Broome Street, Soho Stake, 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7011, 131 Prince Street, 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7005 / 7112, 200 Sixth Avenue, 1971-1974 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7110, 205 West 57th Street, Messing Residence, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7107, 34 St. Marks Place, East Side Book Store, 1969-1971 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7106, 133 Prince Street, Prince-Wooster Artists' Coop, 1971-1976 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7203, Wyoming Building, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7202, 307-309 West Broadway, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7201, Tel Aviv Delicatessen, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7126, John Lennon and Yoko Ono, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7125, 230 East 97th Street, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7832, 1200 Broadway, 1977-1980 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7833, 366 Broadway, 1978-1980 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7829, 361 West 36th Street, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7830, 32 West 86th Street, undated (Box 18)
  - Job: 7831, 335 Greenwich Street, 1978-1980 (Box 18)
  - Job: 7817, 55 Liberty Street, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7814, 714 Broadway, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7819, 136 Greene Street, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7825, 165-169 Spring Street, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7824, 161 Perry Street, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7821, 45 East 68th Street, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7820, 3 York Street, 1978-1985 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7828, 131 Greene Street, 1978-1981 (Box 19)
  - 472-474 Broome Street, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7826, 40 East 74th Street, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7831, 335 Greenwich Street, 1977-1991 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7816, 54 Bleecker Street, 1978-1985 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7815, 15-17 East 16th Street, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7813, 93 Mercer Street, 1978-1982 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7811, 148 West 23rd Street, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7809, 29 East 22nd Street, 1978-1981 (Box 19)
  - Job: 7810, 10 Beach Street, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7806, 14 West 11th Street, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7805, 9-11 Maiden Lane, 1968-1980 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7803, 74 Broad Street / Job 7805, 9-11 Maiden Lane, undated (Box 20)
  - Job: 7912, 24 West 12th Street, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7917, 20 East 20th Street, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7778, 445-451 Broome Street, 1980-1992 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7777, Village Voice, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7776, 533 Greenwich Street, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7779, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7780, 35 Mercer Street, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7781, 58 West 15th Street, 1977-1979 (Box 20)
  - Job: 7803, 74 Broad Street, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7802, Harley Street Medical Group, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7801, 289 Bleecker Street, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7800, Miscellaneous Jobs 1978 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7782, 60 West 15th Street, 1977-1979 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7868, 543 Broadway, 1978-1993 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7900, Miscellaneous Jobs 1979 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7902, 135 Wooster Street, 1971-1979 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7903, 151 West 28th Street, 1979-1980 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7904, 12 White Street, 1979-1980 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7906, 81 Leonard Street, 1979-1992 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7809, 74 Fifth Avenue, 1979-1981 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7901, 380 West 12th Street, 1979-1981 (Box 21)
  - Job: 7927, 129 West 22nd Street, 1976-1987 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7928, 427 Washington Street, 1978-1979 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7929, 120 West 20th Street, 1979-1980 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7930, 75 Horatio Street, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7931, Grooms Loft, undated (Box 22)
  - Job: 7924, 105-113 Wooster Street, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7932, Hard Rock Cafe, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7933, 759 Greenwich Street, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7847, 45 East 68th Street, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7847, 644 Greenwich Street, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7848, 128 East 65th Street, 1978-1980 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7851, 441 Lafayette Street, 1979-1981 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7926, 491 Broadway, 1982-1989 (Box 22)
  - Job: 7921, 101 Wooster Street, 1979-1980 (Box 23)
  - Job: 7922, 29 East 10th Street, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Job: 7923, 153-159 West 15th Street, 1979-1981 (Box 23)
  - Job: 7924, 105 Wooster Street, 1980 (Box 23)
  - Job: 7926, 471 Broadway, 1983-1988 (Box 23)
  - Job: 7925, 27 West 67th Street / Miscellaneous Projects, 1979-1986 (Box 23)
  - Job: 7865, 361 West 36th Street, 1979-1983 (Box 23)
  - Job: 7866, 59 Wooster, 1979-1983 (Box 23)
  - Job: 7853, 485 Broome Street, 1978-1980 (Box 24)
  - Job: 7855, 121 Mercer Street, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Job: 7856, Whitney Museum, 1978 (Box 24)
  - Job: 7857, 125 Prince Street, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
  - Job: 7858, 21 Bond Street, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
  - Job: 7859, 135 Greene Street, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Job: 7860, 137 Greene Street, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
  - Job: 7861, 39 Great Jones Street, 1980-1982 (Box 24)